(Raj:)But she did dump you.
(Howard:)Grow up, Raj.
There's no place for truth on the Internet.
(Howard:)Just go. I'll catch up with you.
All right.
(Raj:)We should have a plan
in case one of us gets lucky.
(Leonard:)Okay, uh...
(Leonard:)If I get lucky, I'll take her to my stately
manor outside Gotham City...
(Leonard:)...and if you get lucky,
I'll sleep on the moon.
(Raj:)Sounds like a plan.
(Penny:)Hang on, I think the emergency key
is around here somewhere.
(Sheldon:)We have a bowl.
(Sheldon:)Our keys go in a bowl.
(Sheldon:)You should get a bowl.
(Penny:)So how did the beautiful mind of Sheldon
Cooper forget his key in the first place?
(Sheldon:)I left them in the bowl.
Uh-oh. I remembered
where the emergency key is.
- Where?
- In your apartment.
(Sheldon:)What's it doing in my apartment?
(Penny:)I went in there a few weeks ago,
and you guys weren't home, and I forgot it.